Guide to the J. B. Fuqua Papers, 1929-2006 and undated RL.00426
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 2008-0024
  - Home Office Files
    - E.D.P. Leasing Corporation Folder - EDP Prospectus and correspondence regarding possibly purchase of Statistical Services Corp. by NATCO, 1966 (Box 88)
    - WQAD - Moline TV Corp Folder - Reports and correspondence regarding WQAD, 1966 (Box 88)
    - Collection of unfoldered Press releases, memos, newspaper clippings, Fuqua's Resume, and other materials, 1968-1974 (Box 88)
    - Fall 1970 edition of Snowmobile Magazine, 1970 (Box 88)
    - Script of speech J. B. FUQUA BEFORE NEW YORK SOCIETY OF SECURITY ANALYSTS MARCH 1, 1972 (Box 88)
    - Atlanta Constitution News clipping, March 23, 1972, regarding Fuqua and others in Movie Venture (Box 88)
    - Two (2) copies of Fernquest & Johnson (a Fuqua Industry) Golf club catalog, 1971 (Box 88)
      Note FROM THE DESK OF BEVERLY DEMPSEY addressed to Winona (Fuqua's Secretary) attached to front of one of the catalogs.
    - Rough copy summary of multiple companies for Fuqua Industries annual report, 1972 (Box 88)
    - Stock/investment summary of Fuqua Industries by A. G. Edwards & Sons with letter from FI Director of Advertising letting all FI subsidiary Presidents know the annual report would soon be released, 1972 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence regarding Correction/Changing of Portrait made of Fuqua, 1969-1970 (Box 88)
    - Letters from Winona Warner to Abercrombie and Fitch requesting appointment diaries, 1967-1968 (Box 88)
    - LAKE McCLURE WOODS AND PARK Information Kit Folder - contains 1968 Fuqua Industries Annual Report and other materials, 1968 (Box 88)
    - Photocopy of The Value Line Investment Survey Summary of Advices and Index for Dec. 24, 1971 (Box 88)
    - UNITED STATES GUARANTY Life Insurance Company docs for a policy on Fuqua, 1956 (Box 88)
    - Copy of Sales agreement b/n WEHT and Fuqua for WEOA radio, 1961/1972 (Box 88)
      Letter to Winona attached to front indicating she had requested a copy from Harold Poole.
    - Unidentified light blue folder - Assorted materials regarding Fuqua, Fuqua Industries, NATCO, 1966-1967 (Box 88)
    - J. B. Fuqua Folder - Report on Royal Crown soda business (Box 88)
    - Royal Crown Bottling Co. Envelope - Photographs of Royal Crown Bottling Co. Building and August, 1945, copy of Nehi News (Box 88)
    - Copy of The Executive's Quotation Book: A Corporate Companion, James Charlton, Ed., 1983 (Box 88)
    - 49 printed and saddle stitched copies of Fuqua's 1986 Commencement Address at Oglethorpe University, 1986 (Box 89)
    - Two Fake Trillion dollar bills with picture of Kemmons Wilson on front, 1992 (Box 89)
    - JB Fuqua ATLANTA ANALYSTS 2-3-1971 miniature audio tape (Box 89)
    - MARKETING IN MOTION 1986 MARKETING STATESMAN OF YEAR - JB FUQUA miniature audio tape (Box 89)
    - ROTARY Club Augusta 6-1-1986 miniature audio tape, 1986 (Box 89)
    - JB FUQUA Leadership miniature audio tape (Box 89)
    - Unidentified miniature audio tape (Box 89)
    - Assorted news clippings, news letters, reports and other materials in Fuqua's Speech file, 1990-1997 (Box 89)
    - Printed and saddle stitched copy of The Story of Fuqua Industries, Inc. by J.B. Fuqua, 1973 (Box 89)
      Printed copy of address given at the 1972 Georgia Dinner of the Newcomen Society of North America.
    - Copy of The Index of Leading Cultural Indicators: Facts and Figures on the State of American Society, 1994 (Box 89)
    - Longwood College 5/12/1990 Envelope containing printed copy and note cards of address given at Longwood College, 1990 (Box 89)
    - Augusta Rotary Club 3/5/1992 Envelope containing printed notes (for speech?), 1992 (Box 89)
    - Yellow envelope containing notes, printed copies of addresses and assorted other materials regarding speeches (Box 89)
    - THE SUCCESSFUL MBA FSB COMMENCEMENT ADDRESS MAY 16, 1992 Folder containing photocopy of address by Fuqua, 1992 (Box 89)
    - Augusta Chamber of Commerce Speech - Nov. 5, 1990 Folder containing notes for address and correspondence about event at which address was given, 1990 (Box 89)
    - 1990 NCWTA CONFERENCE Speech - 5/9/1990 Folder containing correspondence regarding the 1990 NCWTA Conference (Box 89)
    - The Institute of Financial Education JBF Speech - October 2, 1986 (Box 89)
      Folder containing correspondence and other materials regarding seminar at which Fuqua spoke.
    - American Banker Seminar Feb. 27-28, 1986 (Box 89)
      Folder containing talking notes, correspondence, and other materials regarding conference at which Fuqua spoke.
    - COLUMBIA U. - JBF Speech 3/26/1985 Folder containing notes (Box 89)
    - Snapper Distributor Meeting JBF Speech - July 27, 1983 Folder containing hardcopy of speech by Fuqua (Box 89)
    - Intergrowth '83 JBF Speech - April 18, 1983 Folder containing hardcopy of speech given by Fuqua (Box 89)
    - DUKE- JBF Speech 4/25/1980 Folder containing very brief notes (Box 89)
    - Club Corporation of America JBF Speech - Feb. 1, 1976 Folder containing talking notes and correspondence regarding meeting at which Fuqua spoke (Box 89)
    - Harvard Business School Speech November 6, 1975 Folder notes and correspondence regarding talks at Harvard (Box 89)
    - ON THE LIGHTER SIDE QUOTABLES Binder containing various quote materials (Box 89)
    - PREVIOUS SPEECHES Binder containing hard copies of speeches and notes by Fuqua and others (Box 89)
    - BUSINESS PHILOSOPHIES & PRACTICES Binder containing assorted clippings, pamphlets, etc. (Box 89)
    - Three blue folders containing assorted clippings, pamphlets, speech notes, correspondences and other speech materials (Box 90-91)
    - Copy of The Further Sayings of Chairman Malcolm by Malcolm Forbes, 1986 (Box 91)
    - Copy of An Illustrated Guide to the American Economy by Herbert Stein and Murray Foss, 1992 (Box 91)
    - Two SPEECH IDEAS Folders containing assorted magazines, reports, clippings, pamphlets, etc. (Box 91)
    - THE ECONOMY REAGANOMICS TAXES Binder containing assorted clippings, a book, reports, essays, graphs, correspondence, etc, 1975-1981 (Box 96)
    - STATISTICS MISCELLANEOUS Binder containing clippings/copied articles, notes, pamphlets, etc, 1975-1983 (Box 96)
    - LEADERSHIP - ENERGY Binder containing speeches, pamphlets, clippings, etc., 1977-1980 (Box 96)
    - RENTAVISION OF BRUNSWICK Folder - FCC, financial, and other materials regarding cable TV enterprises, 1965-1966 (Box 92)
    - SOUTHERN BELL Folder - Financial and other info. regarding Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company and its plans to build a Community Antenna Television System in the Brunswick, Georgia, area, 1963-1965 (Box 92)
    - 'OTHER' LEGAL CORRESPONDENCE Folder - Legal correspondence and documents regarding companies' legal actions against Community Antenna Television ventures., 1965 (Box 92)
    - COWART, SAPP, ALAIMO & GALE - CORRESPONDENCE Folder - Correspondence to and from law firm regarding CATV venture legal proceedings and assorted related news clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 92)
    - RENTAVISION OF BRUNSWICK, INC. (Pro Formas, Minutes & Other Information) Folder - assorted materials regarding CATV venture in Brunswick, GA, 1965 (Box 92)
    - Signed minutes of Meeting of Board of Directors KTVE, Inc. dated 6/9/1967, 1967 (Box 92)
    - KTVE expense summary dated 9/12/1967 (Box 92)
    - letter from Jack L. Smith & Co. and contract for same to purchase property the 1st Presbyterian Church, 1964 (Box 92)
    - Contract for building demolition to be done for the 1st Presbyterian Church of Monroe, 1964 (Box 92)
    - Correspondence and legal documents related to KTVE lease negotiations, 1963-1964 (Box 92)
    - KTVE-PROGRAMMING & CONTRACTS Folder - Correspondence, promotional material, financial documents, etc. related to KTVE Programming purchases, 1964-1965 (Box 92)
    - Unidentified folder - KTVE related correspondences and financial documents, 1960-1964 (Box 92)
    - Black cover bound book of KTVE, Inc. stock coupons (Box 92)
    - FAA Folder - Federal Aviation Agency materials regarding Rentavision of Brunswick requests for antenna tower clearance, 1965 (Box 92)
    - CATV - BRUNSWICK, GA. Folder - studies, reports, legal documents, news clippings, and correspondence regarding CATV venture in Brunswick, 1962-1965 (Box 92)
    - S.K.L. - HEAD-END Folder - correspondence, sales contract, pamphlet, etc. regarding antenna tower for Rentavision of Brunswick, Inc., 1965 (Box 92)
    - KTVE - OREN HARRIS Folder - Correspondences to and from Congressman Oren Harris, 1963-1965 (Box 92)
    - CATV Folder - Study report, correspondence, clippings and pamphlets, proposals, receipts, etc. regarding CATV, 1962-1966 (Box 92)
    - KTVE - LEGAL DOCUMENTS, ETC. Folder - Agreement to purchase and other legal documents, meeting minutes, correspondences, notes, balance sheet reports, etc., regarding KTVE, 1960-1967 (Box 92)
    - TO REPLACE PAGE ENTITLED 'STUDIO BUILDINGS' Documents - Appraisal of fixed assets of KTVE replacement pages (Box 93)
    - PROMOTION HOUSE FOR WJBF-TV, 1958 (Box 93)
    - KTVE INC. (Per Haskin and Sells Audit Reports) Three year revenue report, 1961-1963 (Box 93)
    - Two (2) copies of APPRAISAL KTVE, INCORPORATED EL DORADO, ARKANSAS Television Station KTVE-TV, 1965 (Box 93)
    - CHAPTER IX SUMMARY VALUATION OF FUQUA INDUSTRIES TV STATIONS (Box 93)
    - AGREEMENT OF SALE AND PURCHASE of KTVE, Inc. stock, 1963 (Box 93)
    - TELEVISION COVERAGE OF KTVE EL DORADO, ARK map chart with overlays (Box 93)
    - KTVE TRANSFER (& FCC) Folder - Correspondence, legal documents and assorted materials regarding acquisition of KTVE, 1961-1964 (Box 93)
      Two copies of a photo of KTVE included in file.
    - Land Survey of Lot (94 of the Johnsten Subdivision) in El Dorado, Arkansas, 1963 (Box 93)
    - Nielsen Station Index Service informational pamphlet and Agreement/contact, 1964 (Box 93)
    - Collection of correspondences, equipment lease agreement, and other materials regarding KTVE, 1961-1967 (Box 93)
    - KTVE Folder - financial statements, market data report, correspondence, pamphlet, and assort materials regarding KTVE, 1962-1964 (Box 93)
    - KTVE - GSA RENTAL ADVANCED ANS. RENTAL Folder - Correspondences and assorted materials regarding renting space in the KTVE building to assorted businesses, 1964-1967 (Box 93)
    - KTVE - PHOTOS & MAPS Folder - photo of KTVE studio bldg, pamphlets, photos, maps, 1963-1964 (Box 93)
    - KTVE -TRANSFER & FCC) Folder - correspondence, contract for sale, FCC approval forms, financial reports, etc. regarding transfer of control of KTVE to Gray Communications Systems, 1964-1968 (Box 93)
    - SALESMEN'S ACCOUNT LISTS Folder - Correspondences, pamphlets, sales accounts lists, etc. (Box 93)
    - KTVE - PURCHASE Folder - Correspondence regarding purchase of outstanding capital stock of KTVE, Incorporated by Fuqua Industries, Inc., 1962-1964 (Box 93)
    - Unidentified folder - KTVE related correspondences and financial documents regarding closing of loan by Exchange Bank and Trust Co., 1964-1965 (Box 93)
    - KTVE - REPRESENTATION Folder - Contract/Agreement and Correspondence regarding Sales representation of KTVE, 1963-1965 (Box 93)
    - KTVE - EQUIPMENT Folder - Reports, Pamphlets, Contracts and materials regarding Equipment at/for KTVE, 1963-1965 (Box 93)
    - KTVE - TOWER Folder - Correspondence regarding KTVE antenna tower(s) and FAA regulation, 1964 (Box 93)
    - KTVE - INSURANCE Folder - Correspondence, contracts, etc. regarding Insurance policies at KTVE, 1964 (Box 93)
    - KTVE - BANK CORRESPONDENCE Folder -, 1963-1966 (Box 93)
    - Unidentified Light Green Folder - KTVE coverage maps, bank and legal correspondence, 3 copies of Grand of Easement and Servitude, equipment leasing documentation, income statements, and assorted other materials, 1961-1965 (Box 94)
    - KTVE - PUBLICITY Folder - Assorted news clippings related to KTVE, 1963-1965 (Box 94)
    - Television Bureau of Advertising, 5th Anniversary plaque saluting J.B. Fuqua, WJBF (Box 94)
    - WNCT Folder - Correspondence regarding purchase of WNCT, Channel 9, Greenville, NC, 1961 (Box 94)
    - VIDEOTAPE RATES - OTHER STNS. Folder - Correspondences, rate card pamphlets, etc. regarding video tape recording, 1958-1961 (Box 94)
    - Two (2) copies of BEFORE THE FEDERAL COMMUNICATIONS COMMISSION, February 19, 1962 bound Comments, 1962 (Box 94)
    - Assorted FCC documents, supporting materials, and related correspondences regarding proposed new ("drop-in") station in Charlotte (among other locations), 1961-1962 (Box 94)
    - 1968-1969 WORKING PAPERS Envelope - Financial reports/documents regarding WJBF-TV, 1968-1969 (Box 94)
    - 1950 Broadcasting Yearbook, 1950 (Box 95)
    - Television Today: a Report from CBS-TV, 1949 (Box 95)
    - The Long Range Effect of Television and other Factors on Sports Attendance by Jerry N. Jordan, 1950? (Box 95)
    - Two (2) copies of Audit report of Radio Evansville, Inc., WROZ, December 31, 1965, 1965 (Box 95)
    - PUBLIC SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENTS - WJBF 1967 Folder - lists of public service announcements on WJBF, 1967 (Box 95)
    - Assorted correspondence from and to WJBF-TV viewers, 1963-1966 (Box 95)
    - Letter to Fulton National Bank that accompanied payments for mortgage notes of Mr. (Gov.?) Sanders and Fuqua, 1966 (Box 95)
      Reference to Mr. Sanders may refer to Gov. Carl Sanders.
    - The Dual System Editorial on public/private school system(s) from The Atlanta Journal, March 5, 1969, 1969 (Box 95)
    - Letter from William Cooney at Law Office informing Fuqua of permission granted by Augusta-Richmond Board of Zoning Appeals to construct a transmission tower, 1965 (Box 95)
    - 1940s WJBF program ideas advertising budgets Folder - advertising rate cards, photographs, clippings, program ideas, correspondences and other materials regarding program developments and ad sales, 1948-1969 (Box 95)
    - WJBF Call letters Folder - Correspondences, affidavits, and other materials regarding challenge to an Augusta radio station changing its call letters to WJBP, 1968 (Box 95)
    - 1960 Folder - Correspondence to/from WJBF-TV, 1960 (Box 95)
      Letter from U.S. Senator Strom Thurmond regarding my television film clips, a response from Fuqua to Chairman of S.C. Diocesan Council of Catholic Men asking that both laymen and church official of the Catholic faith will stay completely out of the coming political campaign.
    - LETTERS OF APPRECIATION 1966 Folder - Correspondence to/from WJBF-TV, 1966 (Box 95)
      Letter of thanks from congressman Wm. Jennings Bryan Dorn. Letter from Treasury regarding filmed raids on unregistered distilleries, Letters from Army and Navy.
    - 1955-1956-1957 Folder - Correspondence to WJBF-TV, 1955-1956 (Box 95)
    - 1958 Folder - Correspondence to/from WJBF-TV, 1958 (Box 95)
      Letter from Law offices to FCC regarding request of an Augusta Radio Station to change its call letters to WJBP, Letter noting Award to WJBF from the US Secretary of Defense.
    - LETTERS OF APPRECIATION 1969 Folder - Correspondences to WJBF, 1969 (Box 95)
    - Two (2) copies of WGAC: Going Forward with Radio program/informational booklet, 1948 (Box 96)
      Page on NEGRO PROGRAMS.
    - TV OPERATIONS Folder - Clippings, FCC notices, financial reports, pamphlets, prospectus, correspondences, Augusta Newspapers Inc. Annual Reports, 1953-1961 (Box 96)
    - WJBF - TV APPLICATION Folder - Assorted Materials regarding FCC Broadcast License Applications/Renewals/Amendment, 1950-1955 (Box 96)
    - WILLINGHAM FINANCE CO., Inc. brown, spiral bound report - business report on Willingham Finance Co., 1955? (Box 96)
    - Fuqua Offices Binder - Photos, Slides, and other materials regarding the interior design of Fuqua offices in Atlanta AND reprints of a write up on the office design from Corporate Design & Realty, 1983-86 (Box 97)
    - Unidentified Binder of Slides and positives (Advertising shots?) (Box 97)
    - Annual Report Slides Binder - 1986 Annual Report Photo out takes slides, 1986 (Box 97)
    - Qualex Binder - Slides, 1985-90 (Box 97)
    - Recreational Products: NPR Binder - slides, 1979-80 (Box 98)
    - Various Subs Binder - Slides and negatives, 1979-89 (Box 98)
    - Misc. F/I (Fuqua Industries) Slides Binder, 1970-1979 (Box 98)
    - Annual Report Photos & Slides 1988 Binder - Photo reproductions of slides in other binder in Box 14, slides and transparencies, 1988 (Box 98)
    - Fuqua Homes Hutch Nelson/Weather-Rite Snapper Stormor Slides 1985 Binder - Slides, mobile home blueprints/info pamphlets, photos, positives, 1985 (Box 98)
    - Colorcraft Slides 1985 Binder - Slides, photos, positives, 1985 (Box 99)
    - Annual Report slides: 1984-1987 Binder - slides, negatives, positives, photos, 1983-87 (Box 99)
    - Annual Report Photos: 1989 Binder - Strip positives, 1989 (Box 99)
    - Unidentified Binder of Slides, 1986-87 (Box 100)
    - Colorcraft Corp. Binder - slides, 1987 (Box 100)
    - Fuqua Sports Binder - slides, 1978-1979 (Box 100)
    - Photo album (floral with a maroon border) - Pictures and captions regarding Atlanta Olympics water dispensing/beat-the-heat measures assisted by a donation from Fuqua, 1996 (Box 101)
    - Two photo albums (small, rectangle brown) - Pictures from the 1st President's Meeting 1968 Sea Island, Ga., 1968 (Box 101)
    - Photo album (small, rectangle red) - Pictures from the 1976 FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. PRESIDENTS' MEETING The Princess Hotel Acapulco, Mexico, 1976 (Box 101)
    - Photo album (very small, rectangle, maroon) - Pictures from the Daiwa Presentation 5/87, 1987 (Box 101)
    - Photo album (large, square black) - Pictures from an unidentified event (Box 101)
    - SNAPPER POWER EQUIPMENT CO 1983 Album of Slides - Slides of Snapper push and ride on mowers, 1983 (Box 101)
    - SNAPPER PWER EQUIPMENT 1982 Album of slides - Slides of Snapper push and ride on mowers and factory shots, 1982 (Box 101)
    - COLORCRAFT CORP. 1982 Album of slides - Slides of photo development equip, photographers, portraits, 1982 (Box 101)
    - GEORGIA FEDERAL Album of slides - Presentation slides for Georgia Federal (Box 101)
    - Photo album (large, square brown) - Pictures from the Colorcraft Corporation General Management Meeting Acapulco Princess February 1984, 1984 (Box 101)
    - J.B. Fuqua: Geneen and Lunch Video tape - Speech and Q/A on event of unveiling of bust of Fuqua at the School and Lunch, 1989 (Box 102-104)
      Frequent references to Russia/USSR business programs.
    - Weatherford Television: JB Fuqua tribute 4-11-01 Video tape - approx. 1/2 hour history on Fuqua with comment by associates and family, 2001 (Box 102-104)
      Two (2) copies.
    - Atlanta Business Hall of Fame: J.B. Fuqua Laureate Video 3/24/2002 - history of life, 2002 (Box 102-104)
    - Skyland Trail Video tape - mental illness/treatment at Skyland Trail, 2000 (Box 102-104)
    - Robert Schuller with the Hour of Power Video tape - episode w/ Fuqua as guest/interviewee, Two (2) copies, 2002 (Box 102-104)
      Discussion of Fuqua's funding of Schuller's International School of Christian Comms.
    - The J.B. Fuqua Foundation Video tape- Cumberland College appeal for funding and choir concert dedicated to the Fuqua Foundation (Box 102-104)
    - 40th Anniversary WJBF Nov. 11, 1993 JBF & Bob Young - Interview b/n Fuqua and Bob Young on occasion of station 40th anniversary, 1993 (Box 102-104)
    - The Caring Institute: Profiles in Caring Video J.B. Fuqua - Val Halamandaris hosted interview program on people who have dedicated life to others (Box 102-104)
    - Great Georgians: Carl Sanders Video tape - (Box 102-104)
      A cursory review shows no direct comment regarding Fuqua.
    - Horatio Alger Assoc. 1990 Awards Dinner: May 18, 1990 Video tape - Awards to and acceptance speeches by multiple people not including Fugua, 1990 (Box 102-104)
      A cursory review shows no direct comment regarding Fuqua, Fuqua was Alger Award winner
    - Horatio Alger Assoc. Only in America - promotional video (Box 102-104)
      A cursory review shows no direct comment regarding Fuqua, Fuqua was Alger Award winner.
    - Horatio Alger Assoc. 47th Annual (1994) Awards, 1994 (Box 102-104)
      A cursory review shows no direct comment regarding Fuqua. Fuqua was Alger Award winner
    - Horatio Alger Assoc. Presents: One Child, One Dream - 46th Annual (1993) Awards Hosted by Bob Costas, 1993 (Box 102-104)
      A cursory review shows no direct comment regarding Fuqua. Fuqua was Alger Award winner.
    - Foundation of Wesley Woods, Heroes, Saints and Legends 2002 Video tape - celebration of 4 outstanding Senior Georgians including J.B. and Dorothy Fuqua, 2002 (Box 102-104)
      Fuqua's candid discussion of his depression and shock treatment.
    - AGL Resources Presents the 2000 Shining Light Award, J.B. Fuqua, December 12, 2000, 2000 (Box 102-104)
      Russian students to Fuqua commented on by CEO of CNN who introduced Fuqua
    - The Summit: The Fiftieth Anniversary of YPO, Opening Ceremony, Sunday, April 2, 2000, 2000 (Box 102-104)
      Young President's Organization (YPO) documentary, No direct comment regarding Fuqua.
    - The J.B. Fuqua Story by Affordable Video Solutions (Box 102-104)
    - Hall of Fame 2000 Banquet: GSU -(not Fuqua Year) Video tape, 2000 (Box 102-104)
    - Junior Achievement International 'Global Awards & Recognition Luncheon' July 12, 1999 Video tape, 1999 (Box 102-104)
      Tape fast forwarded to part of program in which award bearing Fuqua's name was awarded.
    - Senator Sam Nunn Speech to Carnegie Conference re: U.S.-Russian Nuclear Postures - 6/21/04, 2004 (Box 102-104)
      Recording from C-SPAN, No apparent comment regarding Fuqua, but another piece of data regarding Russia.
    - 1993 SMEI Academy of Achievement Induction Banquet Video tape - Awarding of pinnacle award to multiple awardees including Fuqua, 1993 (Box 102-104)
      Sales and Marketing Executives International.
    - Senator Max Cleland, Larry King Live, 7/6/99 Video tape, 1999 (Box 102-104)
    - Reunion of the 1963 Georgia State Senate, February 23, 1993 Video tape, 1993 (Box 102-104)
    - A Trip Into History, May 12-17, 2002, The Carter Center Video tape, 2002 (Box 102-104)
    - Robert Schuller with the Hour of Power Video tape - show 1462, 1998 (Box 102-104)
    - Robert Schuller with the Hour of Power Video tape - show 1629, 2001 (Box 102-104)
      Letter from Schuller's assistant to the Fuqua included.
    - Hour of Power Video tape, 1990 (Box 102-104)
    - Robert Schuller with the Hour of Power Video tape - show 1603 (Box 102-104)
      Mikhail Gorbachev guest of this episode, Russia/USSR
    - J.B. Fuqua, 'HAPPY BIRTHDAY' Video tape - a look at the life of Fuqua narrated by his son for the occasion of his birthday (Box 102-104)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson Library & Museum, Highlights of the Symposium 'Legacy of the Sixties' May 1999 Video, 1999 (Box 102-104)
      Symposium about Johnson's legacy, relationship with press and congress
    - International School of Christian Communications, January 25-29, 1993 - (before and after?) Sermons given by a number of different people, 1993 (Box 102-104)
      Fuqua funded center
    - International School of Christian Communications, November 12, 1993 - Graduation Ceremony, 1993 (Box 102-104)
      Fuqua funded center.
    - 9-17-02 Brenda Wood Faces of Depression Video tape - Documentary on Depression, 2002 (Box 102-104)
      Includes interview with/profile on J.B. Fuqua
    - DUB FOR: TOM JOHNSON CNN Depression Video tape - Larry King Live episode on depression, 1996 (Box 102-104)
    - TODAY SHOW 7/26/02 TOM JOHNSON Video tape, 2002 (Box 102-104)
      Tom Johnson Interviewed, Mention made of Fuqua's Book.
    - CNN YOUR HEALTH SHOW 3/2/02 Video tape, 2002 (Box 102-104)